bricks.
>> He's the number one player left on my
board at the moment. Uh we do have Devin
Moore on the line, one of the the newest
Dallas Cowboys, the corner from Florida.
Devin, congratulations. You you had a
Florida guy, Brian Shottenheimer, go and
get a Gator. What is this moment like
for you?
Oh, it's everything and more, you know,
to be able to get picked by such a
prestigious organization and uh, you
know, it's America's team. So, you know,
just being able to join that
organization and bring help and get back
to winning games and help them win games
and create a better organization.
>> You met with Dallas at the the NFL
combine there in Indianapolis. What was
that part of the process like for you
and what were some of the conversations
that you had throughout the process with
the Cowboys?
>> Yeah, when I met with them at the
combine, uh, you know, we went over some
of my good plays and plays I could clean
up and, uh, they just picked my brain.
Uh, see if I knew what I was talking
about, uh, talk scheme wise, coverage
wise, you know, even Dline. I showed
them I could get on the board and drop
the Dline, too. And, uh, yeah, they were
impressed. And you know, it was just a
blessing to be able to showcase all the
things that my coaches at the University
of Florida and my coaches before then,
you know, instilled into me and poured
into me and be able to showcase it.
>> Devin, congratulations. Welcome to the
Dallas Cowboys, man. Awesome day for
you. For for Cowboy fans that maybe
didn't get to watch you a ton at
Florida, how would you describe yourself
as a player? And then also maybe some
self- scouting areas that you want to
improve upon.
>> For sure. Yeah. If I had to describe
myself as a player, I'd say a tall,
long, and uh strong DB. You know,
versatile. I could move back and play
some safety. I can also play on the
outside of corner, even move inside in
some cases. And uh you know, I got a lot
of physical features that uh help me on
the field a lot. you know, being long,
fast, big, and then also I pair that
with my mental, but the process is
extremely fast. And also recognize what
the offense is trying to do to attack
us. And, you know, some areas I can
improve on for sure would be, uh, just
off man. You know, at the University of
Florida, we are press heavy team. So, I
didn't get a lot of reps at off man. So,
I could definitely improve in that area.
And, uh, you know, technique. you know,
whether that's tackling, uh, press man,
off man, you know, your technique will
never be perfect. So, you know, that's
always an area of improvement no matter
how good you are at it.
>> Devin, welcome. Welcome. You just
mentioned the the mentals. So, is that
film or is that more so you just get on
the field and you just feel it and just
see what kind of comes to you.
Yeah, that's everything, you know,
that's film. That's also, you know, just
knowing basic football knowledge, that's
knowing concepts, that's knowing, you
know, receiver splits, uh, that's
knowing what type of formation, you
know, most plays are ran out of, if the
running back and tight end are on the
same side, if they're on opposite sides,
you know, it's a whole bunch of, you
know, different variables that, you
know, you need in your arsenal to pull
out when you see those things. And just
cuz you have it in your arsenal, you
also have to be confident enough and,
you know, aware enough to recognize it
when that opportunity does present
itself.
>> Yeah, man. Not going to lie, I was just
looking at the monitors and they kind of
had you labeled as a press man, dude.
And hey, look, man. I watch your film,
dog. You are fantastic in in in zone
also. And you also got some ball hawk
ability as well, bro. So, uh, don't let
him lie to you, man. Keep being great.
>> For sure. I appreciate that.
>> For sure. When you look at your growth,
Devin, and and how you you've continued
to get better during your college
career, where do you feel like one
element of your game took the biggest
step?
>> Yeah, definitely. Uh just technique and
and confidence. you know, the the more
reps you put in, the more reps, live
reps you get in the game, and uh you
know, just the more game experience you
get as a whole, you know, the more
confident you'll play, the more you
recognize certain things that uh has
happened before, and the more mistakes
you make to improve on those and, you
know, not make the same mistakes again.
>> Devin, uh not only is your head coach a
Florida Gator, you now get to reunite
with Shamar James as well at linebacker.
Uh does that excite you? I mean, were
you guys tight? It'd be kind of awkward
if maybe you weren't, but hopefully you
are.
>> Oh, yeah. No, that was my dog. You know,
he uh he came in the same recruiting
class as me. You know, me and Shamar,
you know, we very close. You know, I
still reach out to him, make sure he
good. He does the same. And you I can't
wait to, you know, finally be on the
same team as him again.
>> Incredible stuff, Devin. Congratulations
on this moment. We're excited to have
you here in Dallas. Can't wait to see
what you can do uh and and see what uh
what you got in store for Cowboys
Nation.
Oh,
>> can you repeat that? It cut out a little
bit.
>> Well, I was saying we're saying goodbye
to you here. Appreciate you.
Congratulations on the moment.
>> Oh, yeah. Thank you so much. I
appreciate you for having me on.
>> Absolutely. Deon Moore, newest Dallas
Cowboy, pick number 114 in the 2026 NFL
draft.